<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><feed xmlns='http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom' xmlns:openSearch='http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearchrss/1.0/'><id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-11910755</id><updated>2007-10-04T17:32:37.662-04:00</updated><title type='text'>The Fair Skinned Italians</title><link rel='alternate' type='text/html' href='http://www.thefairskinneditalians.com/'/><link rel='next' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://www.blogger.com/feeds/11910755/posts/default?start-index=26&amp;max-results=25'/><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://www.blogger.com/feeds/11910755/posts/default'/><link rel='http://schemas.google.com/g/2005#feed' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://www.thefairskinneditalians.com/feeds/main-atom.xml'/><author><name>Josh</name></author><generator version='7.00' uri='http://www.blogger.com'>Blogger</generator><openSearch:totalResults>77</openSearch:totalResults><openSearch:startIndex>1</openSearch:startIndex><openSearch:itemsPerPage>25</openSearch:itemsPerPage><entry><id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-11910755.post-6097910442610922219</id><published>2007-10-01T13:06:00.000-04:00</published><updated>2007-10-01T13:09:24.252-04:00</updated><title type='text'>Special note to FSI feed readers...</title><content type='html'>We're doing some dusting around the site and want to make sure you're using our latest RSS feed address. Here it is: http://feeds.feedburner.com/TheFairSkinnedItalians&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thanks for following!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Josh</content><link rel='alternate' type='text/html' href='http://www.thefairskinneditalians.com/2007/10/special-note-to-fsi-feed-readers.html' title='Special note to FSI feed readers...'/><link rel='replies' type='text/html' href='http://www.blogger.com/comment.g?blogID=11910755&amp;postID=6097910442610922219' title='0 Comments'/><link rel='replies' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://www.thefairskinneditalians.com/feeds/main-atom.xml' title='Post Comments'/><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://www.blogger.com/feeds/11910755/posts/default/6097910442610922219'/><link rel='edit' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://www.blogger.com/feeds/11910755/posts/default/6097910442610922219'/><author><name>Josh</name></author></entry><entry><id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-11910755.post-5866334049620373344</id><published>2007-09-12T23:53:00.000-04:00</published><updated>2007-09-13T00:00:42.801-04:00</updated><title type='text'>Photo update</title><content type='html'>Lauren and I (sans Remy, sadly) are headed out this weekend for the yearly Petrella/Robinson/Teague beach trip to Seaside -- cannot wait!  Here's a couple sets of photos you may haven't seen yet to keep you occupied...&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://picasaweb.google.com/joshteague/JeanineKembleSBDayParty"&gt;Jeanine &amp; Kemble's B-day party&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://picasaweb.google.com/joshteague/TechVsSamford"&gt;Tech vs. Samford&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Look for more photos (and hopefully some video) here after we get back!</content><link rel='alternate' type='text/html' href='http://www.thefairskinneditalians.com/2007/09/photo-update.html' title='Photo update'/><link rel='replies' type='text/html' href='http://www.blogger.com/comment.g?blogID=11910755&amp;postID=5866334049620373344' title='0 Comments'/><link rel='replies' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://www.thefairskinneditalians.com/feeds/main-atom.xml' title='Post Comments'/><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://www.blogger.com/feeds/11910755/posts/default/5866334049620373344'/><link rel='edit' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://www.blogger.com/feeds/11910755/posts/default/5866334049620373344'/><author><name>Josh</name></author></entry><entry><id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-11910755.post-1221453231256968727</id><published>2007-09-02T00:29:00.002-04:00</published><updated>2007-09-02T00:49:34.670-04:00</updated><title type='text'>Say hello to Remy.</title><content type='html'>&lt;object width="425" height="350"&gt;&lt;param name="movie" value="http://www.youtube.com/v/FJYd2Jvm1uM"&gt;&lt;/param&gt;&lt;param name="wmode" value="transparent"&gt;&lt;/param&gt;&lt;embed src="http://www.youtube.com/v/FJYd2Jvm1uM" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" wmode="transparent" width="505" height="336"&gt;&lt;/embed&gt;&lt;/object&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="font-style:italic;"&gt;The story...&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After Lauren and I got back from San Francisco this summer, we decided it was time to get our very own puppy.  So we did just that.  We snatched this little guy up from the GA Humane Society and we just love him.  His quirky personality is matched only by the supreme amount of toes on his feet -- a grand total of 22.  Officially, we don't know what breed he is, but the main word from his foster parents is "Jack Russell Terrier... mix".  And "mix" is where it gets interesting.  The official &lt;span style="font-style:italic;"&gt;papers&lt;/span&gt; state that he is a Saint Bernard (they're known to have six toes on each foot -- an "undesirable trait" for breeders as we later read), but when we questioned the foster parents about this, they said, "well, he could also be a Chihuahua".  So who knows... but we're going with Jack Russell and we're naming him Remy.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's a few more pictures from his first few weeks with us.  Hope you enjoy them!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;embed type="application/x-shockwave-flash" src="http://picasaweb.google.com/s/c/bin/slideshow.swf" width="505" height="336" flashvars="host=picasaweb.google.com&amp;captions=1&amp;noautoplay=1&amp;RGB=0x000000&amp;feed=http%3A%2F%2Fpicasaweb.google.com%2Fdata%2Ffeed%2Fapi%2Fuser%2Fjoshteague%2Falbumid%2F5103927261866651041%3Fkind%3Dphoto%26alt%3Drss" pluginspage="http://www.macromedia.com/go/getflashplayer"&gt;&lt;/embed&gt;</content><link rel='alternate' type='text/html' href='http://www.thefairskinneditalians.com/2007/09/say-hello-to-remy.html' title='Say hello to Remy.'/><link rel='replies' type='text/html' href='http://www.blogger.com/comment.g?blogID=11910755&amp;postID=1221453231256968727' title='4 Comments'/><link rel='replies' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://www.thefairskinneditalians.com/feeds/main-atom.xml' title='Post Comments'/><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://www.blogger.com/feeds/11910755/posts/default/1221453231256968727'/><link rel='edit' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://www.blogger.com/feeds/11910755/posts/default/1221453231256968727'/><author><name>Josh</name></author></entry><entry><id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-11910755.post-6926449813571239291</id><published>2007-07-05T12:41:00.000-04:00</published><updated>2007-07-05T13:07:51.658-04:00</updated><title type='text'>Whoops.</title><content type='html'>There's this guy that I've run into a number of times on the street.  He never thinks twice about coming up to me [Josh] and giving me his little act.  Here goes...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;---- Two months ago. ----&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Man: [Walking with me down the street] "Hey, hey, how's it going?  What's happenin' man?"&lt;br /&gt;Me:  "Not too much, thanks."&lt;br /&gt;Man: "Hey, those are some nice shoes. You know what?  I bet I can tell you where you got those shoes?"&lt;br /&gt;Me:  "Oh yeah?  Where?"&lt;br /&gt;Man: "You got 'em on your FEET!"&lt;br /&gt;Me:  "Oh you got me good.  Thanks.  Listen, sorry but I've gotta run."&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;---- Three weeks later. ----&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;[Same guy, same act.  Me alone again. Story picks up at the "shoes" question]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Me:  [laughing to myself]&lt;br /&gt;Man: "Hey don't laugh, don't laugh, don't -- I can tell you where you got your shoes!"&lt;br /&gt;Me:  "I can to.  I got 'em on my feet."&lt;br /&gt;Man:  [bewildered. an "oh-my-goodness-whoops-i've-played-this-guy-before" look on his face] "Ok, Ok, Ok, here's another one.  What's the best nation in the world?"&lt;br /&gt;Me:  "Hmm.... best nation.  I don't know, what's the best nation in the world?"&lt;br /&gt;Man:  [Silly grin on his face now -- "Got him!"] "Donation -- thats the best nation"&lt;br /&gt;Me:  "Thanks, but I have no cash with me.  Sorry."&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;---- Last week. ----&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;[Lauren with me this time. I see him walking up to us.  Oh boy.  The man goes through his act.]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Me: "On my feet!" (Wham!)&lt;br /&gt;Man: [bewildered]&lt;br /&gt;Me: "I know... Donation (Bam!).  And hey I've got one for you this time." &lt;br /&gt;Man: [_really_ confused look on his face]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*At this point my mind went blank as I tried to remember this little joke that Lauren's dad used to tell -- the perfect would-be retort for this guy on the street.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Me:  [nudging lauren] "What is it?"&lt;br /&gt;Lauren: [looking at man] "I bet I can tell you how many kids your dad had."&lt;br /&gt;Man: [totally confused] "How many?"&lt;br /&gt;Me:  "None.  Your dad didn't have any.  Your mom did." [smiles -- success!]&lt;br /&gt;Man: "what?"&lt;br /&gt;Me:  [repeat punchline]&lt;br /&gt;Man: "Hey that's not funny man, my mother is dead."&lt;br /&gt;Lauren and I:  [oh no, he think this is a "mom joke" -- ABORT! ABORT!]&lt;br /&gt;Me:  "Sorry man we gotta go, take it easy."&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So thats it . . . the same guy on the street walking with me/us each time down the sidewalk with the same act.  We thought we'd have our turn, and we took it -- but he thought we were making fun of his mother when we were really only just stating a fact.  Alas!</content><link rel='alternate' type='text/html' href='http://www.thefairskinneditalians.com/2007/07/whoops.html' title='Whoops.'/><link rel='replies' type='text/html' href='http://www.blogger.com/comment.g?blogID=11910755&amp;postID=6926449813571239291' title='9 Comments'/><link rel='replies' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://www.thefairskinneditalians.com/feeds/main-atom.xml' title='Post Comments'/><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://www.blogger.com/feeds/11910755/posts/default/6926449813571239291'/><link rel='edit' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://www.blogger.com/feeds/11910755/posts/default/6926449813571239291'/><author><name>Josh</name></author></entry><entry><id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-11910755.post-305619803328526254</id><published>2007-07-02T19:11:00.000-04:00</published><updated>2007-07-02T19:39:55.330-04:00</updated><title type='text'>San Fran Update</title><content type='html'>Well, I've been here for one month as of today. Happy One Month Living in San Francisco Anniversary to me!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;My idea is to post about some of the colorful characters I've seen around the city.* &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There's the Balance Guy. He stands perfectly still on a crate, box, or on his head on a  bottle. He's actually quite good. He only moves his hand to shake his tip cup so you know his goal.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Ho Guy. He dresses up in a Zebra Suit- not like an actual zebra, that could be funny. No, a 'business' suit made of fake zebra skin. He shouts "Ho!" over and over all day, pointing to ladies walking by. He also has a tip cup. But I'm willing to guess his may contain spit or threat notes.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Bush Guy. He dresses like a bush near the Wharf. On my FIRST day here, Josh and I noticed a crowd of people staring towards us. We also saw an older lady being helped to her feet. Assuming we were not the focus of the stares, but rather the fallen elderly, we jumped as a 'bush' reached out and grabbed Josh's arm. The crowd erupted into laughter. Meanies. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There was the guy who rode his bike down the sidewalk yelling "Wheeeeeee" as he coasted down the hill. A grown man. Probably in his forties.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We also saw Bill Clinton. For real. With about 8 security men around him, earpieces and all. He was eating ice cream. We found out he was in town for Pride Day.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(Actually, to be honest, I saw the back of his head. I think I almost ran into him, but was talking to Jen Van Hill. Jeremy was the one who recognized what was going on and yelled to us "That's Bill Clinton!" One of the security guys turned around to stare Jeremy down and make sure he was unarmed.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;But the Winner for all weird things I have seen in this city- including the ones I didn't mention- is.... Walgreens Girl.&lt;br /&gt;There was a girl paying at the Walgreens counter who was wearing a tank top, flip flops, and her &lt;span style="font-style:italic;"&gt;underwear&lt;/span&gt;. Yes, that's right, her underwear. &lt;br /&gt;It was like being in someone's nightmare where they dream they forgot to put on their pants before going out in public. Except that she appeared to be wide awake and unabashed. WEIRDO. and Winner.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And although we didn't see the last event, it's worth a mention. And does involve on of the five senses.&lt;br /&gt;One thing I have learned this month: How to Identify the Smell of Marijuana.&lt;br /&gt;I'm not trying to show off how sheltered I am, but- I am. &lt;br /&gt;And I hadn't really known for sure what it smells like before this city. Now, not only can I identify it, I'm actually very good at it. I could be an undercover cop and would have made tens of arrests by now.&lt;br /&gt;Last night, it was so bad in our apartment- yes our apartment, my supposed sanctuary from all these weird, and illegal- we had to call the front desk. One of our neighbors was being irresponsible and the overwhelming smell was coming through the vents.&lt;br /&gt;So I guess they win for Weirdest Neighbors. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As you can see, it's been an entertaining month. Let's see what July holds.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*My guilt issue is that I truly believe some of the most coloful characters I've seen are ill and need professional help. So I stuck to people that I think are just silly/crazy, not actually crazy/crazy. (But if you want to know the others, let me know. I'll rock your world.)</content><link rel='alternate' type='text/html' href='http://www.thefairskinneditalians.com/2007/07/san-fran-update.html' title='San Fran Update'/><link rel='replies' type='text/html' href='http://www.blogger.com/comment.g?blogID=11910755&amp;postID=305619803328526254' title='2 Comments'/><link rel='replies' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://www.thefairskinneditalians.com/feeds/main-atom.xml' title='Post Comments'/><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://www.blogger.com/feeds/11910755/posts/default/305619803328526254'/><link rel='edit' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://www.blogger.com/feeds/11910755/posts/default/305619803328526254'/><author><name>Lauren</name></author></entry><entry><id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-11910755.post-4127207973366028290</id><published>2007-06-27T01:58:00.000-04:00</published><updated>2007-06-27T02:20:45.232-04:00</updated><title type='text'>Visitors!</title><content type='html'>This weekend our friends the Van Hills came into town to visit.  Here's some photos from our day of fun in the city.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And in case you've missed 'em, you can always find &lt;a href="http://picasaweb.google.com/joshteague/"&gt;the latest photos here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;embed type="application/x-shockwave-flash" src="http://picasaweb.google.com/s/c/bin/slideshow.swf" width="505" height="336" flashvars="host=picasaweb.google.com&amp;RGB=0x000000&amp;feed=http%3A%2F%2Fpicasaweb.google.com%2Fdata%2Ffeed%2Fapi%2Fuser%2Fjoshteague%2Falbumid%2F5080233341371421793%3Fkind%3Dphoto%26alt%3Drss" pluginspage="http://www.macromedia.com/go/getflashplayer"&gt;&lt;/embed&gt;</content><link rel='alternate' type='text/html' href='http://www.thefairskinneditalians.com/2007/06/visitors.html' title='Visitors!'/><link rel='replies' type='text/html' href='http://www.blogger.com/comment.g?blogID=11910755&amp;postID=4127207973366028290' title='1 Comments'/><link rel='replies' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://www.thefairskinneditalians.com/feeds/main-atom.xml' title='Post Comments'/><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://www.blogger.com/feeds/11910755/posts/default/4127207973366028290'/><link rel='edit' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://www.blogger.com/feeds/11910755/posts/default/4127207973366028290'/><author><name>Josh</name></author></entry><entry><id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-11910755.post-1995193700735450117</id><published>2007-06-12T15:18:00.001-04:00</published><updated>2007-06-12T17:55:44.124-04:00</updated><title type='text'>First Impressions</title><content type='html'>As usual, I have no pictures. I really need to learn how to include those. Another goal for this summer.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So here's what I'm noticing about San Fran. For your convenience, I've split it up into pros and cons for those of you who are thinking of moving/visiting. Keep in mind that all of the below are the opinions of one surburbanite girl and not necessarily those of San Francisco locals.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Pros:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'm with Josh again!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Everything I could ever  need is within walking distance. Specifically: Walgreens is on my block, Starbucks is two blocks over. Easy.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'm walking everywhere, and therefore feel much less guilt about the non-existent exercise routine I've been following.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It's never rainy. Everytime I check the Five Day forecast, there's five little suns.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Britex Fabrics. Love it, love it, love it.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;H &amp; M. See above.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are HUGE Gaps, Macys, American Eagle, etc. Ones that cover an entire block. Why walk when you can shop the whole way downtown?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;REALLY nice people work here. Really nice. All the service people are incredibly friendly. Example: I got a free scarf in Chinatown this morning for buying fabric. It was a fabric store. I was fulfilling the customer's purpose. Yet, they deemed me worthy of a scarf. It even coordinated with my outfit.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Amazing food. And Chinatown and Little Italy fall under this umbrella.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Westfield Mall. They must have 5 specialty chocolate stores.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The tourists- some of them are from Europe. I love getting behind them on the sidewalk and listening to them speak. I can't understand the words, but I like the entusiasm.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cons:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You guessed it- there's a huge, huge, HUGE homeless population here. When I say huge, I mean that during a five block walk there's absolutely no surprise to see 10-15 people living on the street. Most of them just hold an empty cup- a few tell you a story. It makes me so sad because there must be a few who are legitimate, but I'm not clever enough to discern those from the ones who are seen walking into package stores.&lt;br /&gt;(*See stories below.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The smells. I'm sure it's the same in any city, though. You'll be walking along, one minute smelling some delicious Italian food, and then all the sudden, this horrid smell smacks you in the face and sucks the air right out of your lungs. Then you take small breaths until you find a clear spot again. Sometimes it takes half a block. Particularly uncomfortable when you've been walking for awhile and are a little winded anyway.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The people who ask for directions. I guess it's a good thing that I am starting to blend into the San Francisco world where people can't identify me as a non-local, but I never know where anything is. Not so helpful.  I get lost in Marietta, don't they know?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The spitting. Oh my goodness, the spitting. Groomed, young, old, homeless, it doesn't matter- men in this city have a hard time swallowing. They especially like to spit just behind me. Any gentleman points they earned by letting me go ahead are lost after they make that disgusting sound and let loose.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Final Thoughts:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It's been an interesting week adjusting to being in a new city. My days are spent sewing, walking to do errands or lunch, or just sitting in the square reading or people watching. It's relaxing, and so strange to get used to after teaching full time. I'm not complaining about having free time- that was something I was craving as the school year wrapped up.&lt;br /&gt;In truth, the hardest part has been knowing I won't be hanging out with any of you for awhile. I miss our family and friends!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;But I am with Josh, and he's taking great care of me. There's some cool pictures he's been taking around the city. I can't attach a link either, but if you go down to the previous post, there's one there.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I hope you're all having a great summer!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*Here's two stories of some of my encounters. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;"I have money, I just need some quarters to make a phone call."- same man seen standing by same phone booth two nights in a row&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Today a man was walking past me on a crosswalk with a lit cigarette in one hand and a brown package in the shape of a bottle in the other. ( I forgot to mention in the cons that cigarette smoke is often blown into your face.) Just before he reached me, he spit (spat?) about a foot in front of me. Some droplets of it hit my hand. It's okay, it's okay- I had Purell that I bought my first week here for just such an occasion.</content><link rel='alternate' type='text/html' href='http://www.thefairskinneditalians.com/2007/06/first-impressions_12.html' title='First Impressions'/><link rel='replies' type='text/html' href='http://www.blogger.com/comment.g?blogID=11910755&amp;postID=1995193700735450117' title='0 Comments'/><link rel='replies' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://www.thefairskinneditalians.com/feeds/main-atom.xml' title='Post Comments'/><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://www.blogger.com/feeds/11910755/posts/default/1995193700735450117'/><link rel='edit' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://www.blogger.com/feeds/11910755/posts/default/1995193700735450117'/><author><name>Lauren</name></author></entry><entry><id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-11910755.post-3249180059735095362</id><published>2007-05-20T23:07:00.000-04:00</published><updated>2007-06-27T02:22:02.073-04:00</updated><title type='text'>Summer Photos</title><content type='html'>Hi friends. If you're interested in viewing photos from our summer out here in S.F., you're going to want to &lt;a href="http://picasaweb.google.com/joshteague/"&gt;visit this page&lt;/a&gt; for the latest updates.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'll be honest -- right now the pickings are pretty slim. Hardly any photos of people you know. Most of it is from my people watching around the city and me playing with my camera.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Below is a sampling of what you can expect to find. The sea lion photos are for the niece and nephew fans of ours . . . taken in effort to alleviate any trauma that may have been done by showing them &lt;a href="http://www.thefairskinneditalians.com/2007/05/gone-fishin.html"&gt;sad Aunt Lauren&lt;/a&gt; a few posts back. :)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;embed type="application/x-shockwave-flash" src="http://picasaweb.google.com/s/c/bin/slideshow.swf" width="505" height="336" flashvars="host=picasaweb.google.com&amp;RGB=0x000000&amp;feed=http%3A%2F%2Fpicasaweb.google.com%2Fdata%2Ffeed%2Fapi%2Fuser%2Fjoshteague%2Falbumid%2F5066556854725599841%3Fkind%3Dphoto%26alt%3Drss" pluginspage="http://www.macromedia.com/go/getflashplayer"&gt;&lt;/embed&gt;</content><link rel='alternate' type='text/html' href='http://www.thefairskinneditalians.com/2007/05/summer-photos_20.html' title='Summer Photos'/><link rel='replies' type='text/html' href='http://www.blogger.com/comment.g?blogID=11910755&amp;postID=3249180059735095362' title='0 Comments'/><link rel='replies' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://www.thefairskinneditalians.com/feeds/main-atom.xml' title='Post Comments'/><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://www.blogger.com/feeds/11910755/posts/default/3249180059735095362'/><link rel='edit' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://www.blogger.com/feeds/11910755/posts/default/3249180059735095362'/><author><name>Josh</name></author></entry><entry><id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-11910755.post-1066929354673574866</id><published>2007-05-08T17:48:00.000-04:00</published><updated>2007-05-08T18:07:03.844-04:00</updated><title type='text'>Meanwhile, Back in Marietta</title><content type='html'>On Thursday, my first day without Josh around, I came home after trying to connect to my school's wireless (unsuccessful). I then realized that I had throughly confused my computer, who then refused to connect to the home wireless. (Not an Apple, obviously.)&lt;br /&gt;Very frustrating, mainly because I know Josh could have fixed it in a heartbeat. However, I can still connect via wire, so I am not complaining. Furthermore, I'm still feeling guilty that I live in America after seeing some of those Idol Gives Back clips. No wireless, no problem.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Then my first weekend without Josh, I left on Friday to go to Mom's, where Katie, John, Mary Ellen, and Caroline babysat me. (Thanks, girls.)&lt;br /&gt;I came back on Sunday just in time to read up before small group (so it's fresh on the mind) when I walked into my bathroom.&lt;br /&gt;The last calm thought I had was that the floors were especially shiny that night.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Then I stepped into a puddle of water that spread throughout the bathroom floor and had formed a small stream into the hallway. (So small, I missed it on my way in.)&lt;br /&gt;The toilet was completely full. And had, evidently, overflooded.&lt;br /&gt;Then comes the best part.&lt;br /&gt;I went into our pantry/storage/laundry room to get the mop, and stepped into another puddle of water.&lt;br /&gt;The nasty toilet water (it may have been clear, but I wasn't fooled) had leaked through the tiled bathroom, under the shower, and into the storage room. Now two rugs were soaked, not to mention a pile of darks. (Don't worry, those were washed twice, Ultra Clean, Level 12)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;However.&lt;br /&gt;Let it be known, I did not cry. I (sort of) calmly called Josh and then the Maintenance Man,  (okay, fine, I called my mom too) who unfortunately didn't have the necessary parts on a Sunday evening to fix said toilet.&lt;br /&gt;I went to small group single, germy, tardy, and unprepared since I never was able to read the chapter for this week. (But I finally got around to mopping the bathroom and storage room.)&lt;br /&gt; I mostly went to learn and grow. A miniscule part of me went because they had a working restroom. TWO even. Spoiled Americans.</content><link rel='alternate' type='text/html' href='http://www.thefairskinneditalians.com/2007/05/meanwhile-back-in-marietta.html' title='Meanwhile, Back in Marietta'/><link rel='replies' type='text/html' href='http://www.blogger.com/comment.g?blogID=11910755&amp;postID=1066929354673574866' title='0 Comments'/><link rel='replies' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://www.thefairskinneditalians.com/feeds/main-atom.xml' title='Post Comments'/><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://www.blogger.com/feeds/11910755/posts/default/1066929354673574866'/><link rel='edit' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://www.blogger.com/feeds/11910755/posts/default/1066929354673574866'/><author><name>Lauren</name></author></entry><entry><id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-11910755.post-3514779631014123938</id><published>2007-05-06T01:53:00.000-04:00</published><updated>2007-05-06T02:05:00.519-04:00</updated><title type='text'>Gone fishin...</title><content type='html'>So tonight I settle into our new &lt;a href="http://thefairskinneditalians.com/summer_home/summer_home.html"&gt;summer home&lt;/a&gt; here in San Francisco.  We're delighted to be right in the heart of the city, near all the shopping locations and many sights.  Lauren won't be here until June, so please take care of her for me in the meantime.  Things are going really well so far and I'm anxious to start &lt;a href="http://www.google.com/"&gt;my internship&lt;/a&gt; this coming Tuesday.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here's what I came home to the other day just before I had to start packing for the trip... so sad.  So sweet.  My wife.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.thefairskinneditalians.com/img/lauren_sad.JPG"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll do our best to keep this site updated with photos and stuff throughout the summer. :)</content><link rel='alternate' type='text/html' href='http://www.thefairskinneditalians.com/2007/05/gone-fishin.html' title='Gone fishin...'/><link rel='replies' type='text/html' href='http://www.blogger.com/comment.g?blogID=11910755&amp;postID=3514779631014123938' title='3 Comments'/><link rel='replies' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://www.thefairskinneditalians.com/feeds/main-atom.xml' title='Post Comments'/><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://www.blogger.com/feeds/11910755/posts/default/3514779631014123938'/><link rel='edit' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://www.blogger.com/feeds/11910755/posts/default/3514779631014123938'/><author><name>Josh</name></author></entry><entry><id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-11910755.post-1119933208198108067</id><published>2007-03-24T11:11:00.000-04:00</published><updated>2007-03-24T12:05:45.512-04:00</updated><title type='text'>Dreams of Nike + iPod</title><content type='html'>Is the sign of a great product when you both dream about it in the same night?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Yesterday I broke in the &lt;a href="http://www.apple.com/ipod/nike/run.html"&gt;Nike+ product&lt;/a&gt; that counts your steps and coaches your workout. And though I didn't do much more than just the basic calibration through a quick walk to the bank, it made enough impact for us both to have wacky dreams about it.  It's a cool little device.  Very smart.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I explained to Lauren how it counted the calories I lost on my walk to and from the bank.  And that would be just about enough for the dreams to work with.  I dreamt that I had decided to walk to Anderson, S.C. to visit our friends Jeremy &amp; Jen.  Half way there, I realized I didn't turn on the iPod, so suddenly, my walk was in vain.  With that knowledge, I took a pit stop along my journey at a nearby "rock farm" to look at all the interesting rocks.  All by myself, just looking at rocks on the ground along this dopey trail.  I woke up soon after I realized what I was dreaming about was a waste of time.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lauren's dream was a bit more frantic.  A quick backstory...  We were at a Luke Mather's birthday party last night and just totally grubbed on all the food all night.  It was so good.  All these brownies, chicken fingers, chips, coke, cake, you name it.  TONS OF FOOD.  Well she dreamed that as we were at the party eating away, her iPod was actually counting the calories she was eating.  It was as if she was standing on a scale throughout the entire party.  As she watched the calorie count reach close to 8,000, she panicked. Thinking the iPod must have been broken, she attempted to restart it, but it came back with the big bold 8,000 calories and counting situation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I can't think of another time when we both dreamed of the same thing in the same night, so maybe it's a sign that Nike and Apple did their job well.</content><link rel='alternate' type='text/html' href='http://www.thefairskinneditalians.com/2007/03/dreams-of-nike-ipod.html' title='Dreams of Nike + iPod'/><link rel='replies' type='text/html' href='http://www.blogger.com/comment.g?blogID=11910755&amp;postID=1119933208198108067' title='2 Comments'/><link rel='replies' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://www.thefairskinneditalians.com/feeds/main-atom.xml' title='Post Comments'/><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://www.blogger.com/feeds/11910755/posts/default/1119933208198108067'/><link rel='edit' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://www.blogger.com/feeds/11910755/posts/default/1119933208198108067'/><author><name>Josh</name></author></entry><entry><id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-11910755.post-5981074729539225029</id><published>2007-03-19T20:24:00.000-04:00</published><updated>2007-03-24T11:07:18.444-04:00</updated><title type='text'>This is all I have....</title><content type='html'>Hello, Friends. I do realize that this blog has been completely forsaken, so I'm going to tell the only things I have to tell...which are more classroom anecdotes. Consider this your fair warning if you're tired of them- that's all you'll find here. =)&lt;br /&gt;Disclaimer done. Here we go.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Last week, a child, whom we'll call Princess,raised her hand to inform me that someone had left mean notes in her desk. One said "Ugly Princess" and one said "you are stuped". Oh, and one of them was signed, "From Lily."&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Now, not only is Lily not quite dim enough to sign her own name to a mean note, but she  also knows how to spell. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So I take a quick handwriting sample from the class. (By the way, did you know stupid is a curse word? When I asked them to write down " you are stupid," they looked at me as if I'd asked them to eat a talking baby rabbit.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The sample narrowed it down to three suspects. One of whom was Princess, who gave me a sample that read "ulgly" and "stoopit"&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To which I was enlightened for the first time to the depths of her street smarts. Her spelling isn't that bad. Substituting an e for an i is one thing...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'll spare you the full TEN MINUTE INTERROGATION that followed. Here's the highlights.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Me: "Princess, did you write these notes to yourself?"&lt;br /&gt;P: "No."&lt;br /&gt;Me:"Are you sure?"&lt;br /&gt;P:"I wouldn't try to frame someone."&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(Mental Me: CAUGHT YOU!)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Me: "Okay...see, that makes me think you did."&lt;br /&gt;P: "I didn't."&lt;br /&gt;Me: "Right...let me show you this. Do you see how you spelled stupid? Well, the person who wrote the note didn't spell it this way. I think you spelled it really wrong on purpose."&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;P:"Did the person spell ugly the same way I did?"&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(YOU'RE REALLY IN IT NOW! I KNOW IT!.. but HOW to convince you that I know it?)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Me: "Actually, no. But it sure looks like they added that extra l in ulgly, doesn't it? Maybe they added it quickly after they wrote the word? Maybe to try to trick me? " &lt;br /&gt;P:" __________" &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(This is old. Moving in for it.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Me:" You know what really makes me think you did it?"&lt;br /&gt;P: "____________"&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Me:" If someone wrote a mean note to me, I'd be crying. And if my teacher thought I did it.. but it wasn't me...I'd be so incredibly sad. But you. You seem more scared that you're getting caught."&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As I'm speaking, Princess is really working to squeeze out some tears. I'm not sure what she was thinking of. But it was very, very sad. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To conclude the story, she finally confessed THE NEXT DAY after I asked her about it once every hour. (Applying the Biblical principle of repeatedly asking for something until the person is worn down and you get it.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Other shorter stories:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After trying to explain who our Ast. Principal is, I had to refer to her outfit before they realized who I was talking about. Which led to a discussion/comparison of her outfit to my outfit.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;"Okay, wait, do you want to talk about my outfit, or do you want to hear the compliment our Ast. Principal gave you?"&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Of course they chose compliment. After going on for about five minutes to pass on the aforementioned compliment, Ed raised his hand.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;"Now can we talk about your outfit?"&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This one's so sad, I'm not sure I should post it. But one day, there was a STENCH in the classroom. I thought one of the boys had a major after lunch moment. Half the class was experiencing a gag reflex.&lt;br /&gt; Hoping it would clear itself- or the mystery child would air him/herself out on the playground, we headed out for recess.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;AFTER OUR 20 MINUTE RECESS, as we're heading in to art, one boy ran up to me and confessed that he'd pooped in his pants.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I guess recess really does beat out just about anything....including comfort and hygiene. (It turns out he was getting over a stomach virus. Poor, self-neglecting kid.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Trying to get the kids thinking about impossible (for our grade, since we don't quite do negatives) math problems, I asked, "If I had five dollars and Bill asked me for 7 dollars, then..."&lt;br /&gt;Student pipes  up, "Then you'd be broke."</content><link rel='alternate' type='text/html' href='http://www.thefairskinneditalians.com/2007/03/this-is-all-i-have.html' title='This is all I have....'/><link rel='replies' type='text/html' href='http://www.blogger.com/comment.g?blogID=11910755&amp;postID=5981074729539225029' title='3 Comments'/><link rel='replies' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://www.thefairskinneditalians.com/feeds/main-atom.xml' title='Post Comments'/><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://www.blogger.com/feeds/11910755/posts/default/5981074729539225029'/><link rel='edit' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://www.blogger.com/feeds/11910755/posts/default/5981074729539225029'/><author><name>Lauren</name></author></entry><entry><id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-11910755.post-1025347585482818045</id><published>2007-01-22T20:19:00.002-05:00</published><updated>2007-01-22T20:58:04.819-05:00</updated><title type='text'>OH no</title><content type='html'>This crazy day began after praying and hoping I would wake up and get to school early to get the week started off well. I was proud of myself when I rolled into the school at 7:20- ten whole minutes early. Excellent for Monday morning.&lt;br /&gt;I had a long mental list of things to do and was feeling like I may get them all done in the 20 minutes I had before the students arrived- and then I saw the fish tank.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;King has passed. And let it suffice to say- it was very obvious very quickly that he was very dead. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thus, a major shift in priorities as instead of making homework packets and centers, I realized I had to get rid of the body before the kids saw and were even more traumatized.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So I grabbed the bowl and ran into the teacher's bathroom. I took the plastic plant out (ew, ew) and tried to ....pour him..... out into the toilet. The only thing that fell out was a large plastic rock.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;First things first. I weighed the option of calling the custodian, but I thought by the time I explained and asked for some kind of scoop or something, too much precious time would have passed. Plus, he would have made fun of me the rest of the year.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I did notice that the water was very bubbly....he'd obviously just cleaned the toilets- the one lucky break in this story- so I rolled up my sleeve and went for it before I could change my germophobic mind.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Plumbing issue avoided. Back to the fish.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The water level in the fishbowl was too low and King sank in between the other plastic rocks. There was no way to pour him out without all the rocks falling out with him. So I did the logical thing and grabbed a handful of paper towels, put them on the floor in a heap and dumped all the remaining contents. I then attempted to cut off all synapse connections as I plucked the plastic rocks away from the discolored bit of flesh until only the fish lay stiffly on the now soaked paper towels.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;With only minutes remaining, I picked up the dripping mess, dumped the fish, flushed,  tried to sop up the small lake I had formed on the floor, sprayed some sort of antiseptic around the entire room, and washed my hands with as much soap as seemed reasonable given the circumstances.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I then ran back to the classroom, hid the bowl, and decided to wait until the right moment to break the news.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Only the thing is, I had two conferences today and in the sprint to prepare for those, forgot to mention it. "It" being the permanent loss of class mascot and continuous writing inspiration. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'll let you know if they don't take the news so well...</content><link rel='alternate' type='text/html' href='http://www.thefairskinneditalians.com/2007/01/oh-no_9319.html' title='OH no'/><link rel='replies' type='text/html' href='http://www.blogger.com/comment.g?blogID=11910755&amp;postID=1025347585482818045' title='9 Comments'/><link rel='replies' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://www.thefairskinneditalians.com/feeds/main-atom.xml' title='Post Comments'/><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://www.blogger.com/feeds/11910755/posts/default/1025347585482818045'/><link rel='edit' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://www.blogger.com/feeds/11910755/posts/default/1025347585482818045'/><author><name>Lauren</name></author></entry><entry><id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-11910755.post-116554871600022305</id><published>2006-12-07T21:51:00.000-05:00</published><updated>2006-12-10T19:16:14.505-05:00</updated><title type='text'>Part III</title><content type='html'>And yet some more...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When I asked Vaughn if his parents signed his permission form to be in the school play,  I got a small insight into their family.&lt;br /&gt;"My dad said I can't do it."&lt;br /&gt;"Oh, okay."&lt;br /&gt;"But my mom said she wants me to."&lt;br /&gt;"Oh."&lt;br /&gt;"My mama told me that she'd be mad at him if he don't let me. She said I'm a play-actor!"&lt;br /&gt;"Ah."&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;One of the student's mothers told me she walked by her son who was standing at attention. When asked what he was doing, he told her he was practicing for the holiday performance. He explained that he had to practice standing for a very long time.&lt;br /&gt;I knew we were drilling too much during those rehearsals.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The kids participate in this computerized reading program where they're always asking me to look up their scores and points. It takes forever to pull up a student's information because you have to open all these windows and click on numerous icons. So imagine what it was like when I was looking up one student's particular score and she stood over my shoulder and narrarated the entire time.&lt;br /&gt;"Yes, now click that...very good, okay...right go over there...no, yes, i meant there....yup, click that...very good...yes, I was going to say to click right there.."&lt;br /&gt;The only thing is that she was about two beats behind the whole time. Kinda like the delay at a football stadium when the referee is talking.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sometimes I turn around and trip over a student who has been standing there the past five minutes. They don't even try to get my attention by actually saying something. This was the case yesterday when I turned and was a little startled because Jen was standing at ready with an uncapped glue stick aimed right towards my nose. She also had a positively thrilled look on her face.&lt;br /&gt;"Mrs. Teague! It smells like cheerios!"&lt;br /&gt;And dadgum, it did.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As part of our Elected Officials lesson, the students were told to describe the characteristics of a good leader. One group (made entirely of girls) decided a princess made a perfect kind of leader. Her desirable characteristic? "Pretty."&lt;br /&gt;Then they illustrated the life sized drawing (yes, a kid laid down on butcher paper and was outlined. Oldie but goodie.)&lt;br /&gt;I noticed the shirt was about a foot away from the skirt.&lt;br /&gt;"Ladies, that shirt seems a little short."&lt;br /&gt;"Oh, it's okay, we're going to draw a belly button."&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Minutes before dismissal, a cell phone went off in class. Yup, a CELL PHONE. I was ready to pounce on someone but everyone seemed shocked. When I narrowed it down to one of two possible bookbags, both girls were white-faced. Finally finding the guilty bookbag, I pulled out a pink phone from Lynn's bag. She was horrified and said her mom must have put it in there.&lt;br /&gt;A story which may be valid because when it rang again and I answered it her mother thought mistook me for Lynn and started talking to me. In Spanish.&lt;br /&gt;I had to get a bilinguil student on the phone to explain that Lynn can't have a cell phone in school. (This was interesting because as always when 2nd graders translate, there's a lot of "what did you tell me to say?")&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And my current favorite:&lt;br /&gt;Remember the anti-social student who asked what color the man was? &lt;a href="http://www.thefairskinneditalians.com/2006/09/classroom-stories-anthology-part-1.html"&gt;(see Part 1)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Unfortunately, he slipped into a spiral of being even more anti-social. To the point where he couldn't even be bribed to work with a partner. He wrote notes to me requesting that he work alone. He preferred to nod or shake his head as communication. He never talked louder than a hoarse whisper. The other students are patient and understanding, but have learned not to expect very much- verbally- from him.&lt;br /&gt;That's all backstory, all of it.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Then yesterday...&lt;br /&gt;The drama club was having an open casting call for the spring play. I explained that if they couldn't stand up on their chair and shout out, "Welcome to our show, everyone!" then they may want to try out next year. Cruel, it seems. I know. Some of the kids were able and willing, some realized they were shy and changed their mind about trying out.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Guess who raised his hand?&lt;br /&gt;"Oh..hmm..honey, do you think you stand on your chair and-"&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As I was still talking, he climbed right up and let his line ring out in a strong, clear voice, "Hey everyone! And welcome to our show!!"&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There was a silence. The room tilted as my brain tried to process what had just happened. My mouth was still open when the classroom spontaneously and unanimously burst into applause. (I think, though I'm not certain, someone even shouted "Bravo")&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;My very own Dead Poets' Society. I have arrived.</content><link rel='alternate' type='text/html' href='http://www.thefairskinneditalians.com/2006/12/part-iii.html' title='Part III'/><link rel='replies' type='text/html' href='http://www.blogger.com/comment.g?blogID=11910755&amp;postID=116554871600022305' title='2 Comments'/><link rel='replies' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://www.thefairskinneditalians.com/feeds/main-atom.xml' title='Post Comments'/><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://www.blogger.com/feeds/11910755/posts/default/116554871600022305'/><link rel='edit' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://www.blogger.com/feeds/11910755/posts/default/116554871600022305'/><author><name>Lauren</name></author></entry><entry><id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-11910755.post-116321969035699859</id><published>2006-11-10T22:31:00.000-05:00</published><updated>2006-11-11T00:16:57.286-05:00</updated><title type='text'>Classroom Stories Part II</title><content type='html'>I don't know if I was just too frazzled last year to notice any humor, or if my former students were simply less interesting. But I find myself laughing (or trying not to, depending on the situation) a lot more this year. Here's a few more classroom stories if you'd like to read on...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I noticed a student rapping the Pledge of Allegiance while the rest of the class was reciting it. Complete with hand gestures, pounding his chest, and giving props to the flag. If it helps to have a mental picture, he's a chubby little Hispanic boy who I believe had the sincerest intentions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;During Community Time, one boy was telling an elaborate story of a church event that took place at the Marietta Diner. He went into great detail about the food that was served, how many people from his church showed up, and how long the table was. He even made a point about how the waiter was surprised to see so many people. ("He saw our table and he was like, 'Whoa!' ") He's a natural entertainer, and the kids were completely into it. When it was time for other students to ask questions, one boy raised his hand. I was thrilled because he's extremely shy and kinda anti-social. Thus began the following conversation.&lt;br /&gt;"What color was the man?"&lt;br /&gt;Long pause. You could see the wheels turning in the story teller's head. He gave up.&lt;br /&gt;"Excuse me?"&lt;br /&gt;"What color was the man?"&lt;br /&gt;"Uh....you mean the waiter?"&lt;br /&gt;"Uh-huh."&lt;br /&gt;"Um......" (At this point, I thought maybe I should intervene, but I'm ashamed to say, I was curious about the answer.)&lt;br /&gt;"Well, he had a gray shirt with a picture of a red truck, a red hat, dark hair, kinda tan skin...."&lt;br /&gt;Close one.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I decided to be ambitious and looked for a class set of a chapter book to read with one of my reading groups. Most of them hadn't read a chapter book yet and I knew they'd be excited. I flipped through the first couple of chapters of Stone Fox. It seemed like a good choice. For days, the students read through the chapters. We were doing all sorts of activities with this story. Character analysis, motivation, author's purpose, the works. It was quite the investment of time and energy.&lt;br /&gt;The last day, we were short on time, so I decided to read the last chapter aloud so we'd have time to finish the book. &lt;br /&gt; I don't know how familiar you are with the book Stone Fox. It's about Little Willy and his dog Searchligh who entered a race to save Grandfather's farm with the prize money. Classic plot. The first eight chapters had been very sweet and uplifting.&lt;br /&gt;So I'm reading through the final chapter. Little Willy and Searchlight are nearing the end of the race. The competitor is right behind and gaining. I'm trying to build the anticipation by practically yelling as I read,&lt;br /&gt; " ' Go, Searchlight, go!' Little Willy yelled. Searchlight went faster and faster, and then, ten feet away from the finish line, her heart burst...... She died instantly. There was no....suffering."&lt;br /&gt;Always, always read the ending of a story before you share it with 7 year olds.*&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Julie came up to me and in one whispered breath said, "Mrs.Teague,mymomsaidthatifmybottomhurts,cuzsometimes&lt;br /&gt;iforgetowipe,thatishouldcallhersoshecantakemetothedoctor."&lt;br /&gt;That was one of those times I knew I could NOT laugh.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I thought the kids were finally over the King the Fish obsession. I was cleaning his bowl while they were at art. When I refilled it, the water seemed really cold, so I left him in a little cup on my desk, assuming the kids wouldn't notice. We only had about 20 minutes until dismissal.&lt;br /&gt;The "line leader" came in the room, immediately came back to me and asked, "Where's King?"&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The kids have this weird, weird thing about touching my shoes whenever they're sitting on the carpet.  And not just one weird kid or two. It's half the class. I never thought I would stop a lesson to whisper, "Please stop touching my shoe." Then a moment later in a firmer whisper, "Sweetie, STOP touching my shoe."&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On the way back from a field trip, I had to fill out a form evaluating the bus driver and her performance. My seat partner was watching me as I filled it out. When I got to the comments section she asked, "what's that mean?"&lt;br /&gt;"It's where I can say nice things about a bus driver."&lt;br /&gt;Pause.&lt;br /&gt;"How about 'she's very pretty.' "&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;During a lesson on symmetry, I drew a heart and split it across with a horizontal line. The goal was to show how if I erased the top half of the heart and drew its mirrored image on the other side of the line, it wasn't the same shape as the pointed bottom half. (Thus disqualifying as a symmetrical line.)&lt;br /&gt; The outcome is that I accidentally drew what looked like part of the female anatomy and had to erase it quickly as the new student started giggling.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*We felt so bad about Searchlight's COMPLETELY unanticipated death that we wrote chapters of our own where she miraculously comes back to life.</content><link rel='alternate' type='text/html' href='http://www.thefairskinneditalians.com/2006/11/classroom-stories-part-ii.html' title='Classroom Stories Part II'/><link rel='replies' type='text/html' href='http://www.blogger.com/comment.g?blogID=11910755&amp;postID=116321969035699859' title='7 Comments'/><link rel='replies' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://www.thefairskinneditalians.com/feeds/main-atom.xml' title='Post Comments'/><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://www.blogger.com/feeds/11910755/posts/default/116321969035699859'/><link rel='edit' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://www.blogger.com/feeds/11910755/posts/default/116321969035699859'/><author><name>Lauren</name></author></entry><entry><id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-11910755.post-116225356338146759</id><published>2006-10-30T18:27:00.000-05:00</published><updated>2006-10-30T21:20:20.630-05:00</updated><title type='text'>Buckhead Church Hardhat Tour</title><content type='html'>Yesterday, along with the Thurmans, Lauren and I had the pleasure of getting to tour the forthcoming home for Buckhead Church.  Like any other North Point/Buckhead event, the polish and attention to detail on the event itself was top notch.  We got to see each of the four floors of the building, as well as the main worship area.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Some interesting tidbits:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;Below the 1st floor is a parking lot that holds as many spots as the current main parking lot holds -- this lot is reserved for Waumba Land / KidStuff families.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Better still, to get to this special parking lot, you actually drive your car/VAN through a tunnel that cuts into building for easy child drop-off. (It is very cool).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There's an escalator system and stairwells &amp; elevators designed just for children (to ensure their safety, etc.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The building is 200,000 Sq. ft.  That means it is really big.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The worship auditorium holds 3-4 times as many attendees as the current one does.  The "upper-deck" seating area alone holds as many as the current in itself.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Beyond these, I can't remember all the other really creative ways they solved certain problems with trying to fit a church in such a place and meet the needs of various groups.&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Finally, what is more impressive to me was Jeff Henderson's (Pastor) 15min. talk he gave to us at the end of the tour.  What stuck out is that in all the planning and fund raising that has gone into the church, they remain cognizant (as we must be) of the fact that the building remains temporal.  He noted that "every church has a closing day" and that one day in the future the building will be sold, abandoned or demoed.  So with that in mind, we must use the space in a great way and to the best of our ability through Jesus.  I thought this was all really forward thinking and very wise.  It made Lauren and I extremely proud of what Buckhead church is doing and how the vision that God has given the leaders there remains laser focused on reaching unbelievers.  Sidenote:  Jeff also remarked how well the Atlantic Station service went earlier in the day -- this is where they've rented a Regal Cinema screen for the morning to beam the service to.  Apparently they packed out every seat (even having to turn away 50 people).  But next week they're going to reserve TWO theater screens for the same thing.  Pretty exciting.  Below are some photos of the worship auditorium in construction.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.thefairskinneditalians.com/photos/buckheadchurch/bc-hires-03.jpg"&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.thefairskinneditalians.com/photos/buckheadchurch/DSCN2442.jpg"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;Above: A view from the upper seating level.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.thefairskinneditalians.com/photos/buckheadchurch/bc-hires-01.jpg"&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.thefairskinneditalians.com/photos/buckheadchurch/DSCN2443.jpg"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;Above: A lateral view across the upper seating level.  Curves rule this building's design to beautiful effect.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.thefairskinneditalians.com/photos/buckheadchurch/bc-hires-02.jpg"&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.thefairskinneditalians.com/photos/buckheadchurch/DSCN2448.jpg"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;br&gt;Lauren and I from the top level.</content><link rel='alternate' type='text/html' href='http://www.thefairskinneditalians.com/2006/10/buckhead-church-hardhat-tour.html' title='Buckhead Church Hardhat Tour'/><link rel='replies' type='text/html' href='http://www.blogger.com/comment.g?blogID=11910755&amp;postID=116225356338146759' title='2 Comments'/><link rel='replies' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://www.thefairskinneditalians.com/feeds/main-atom.xml' title='Post Comments'/><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://www.blogger.com/feeds/11910755/posts/default/116225356338146759'/><link rel='edit' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://www.blogger.com/feeds/11910755/posts/default/116225356338146759'/><author><name>Josh</name></author></entry><entry><id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-11910755.post-116156707393819935</id><published>2006-10-22T21:30:00.000-04:00</published><updated>2006-10-22T21:41:21.173-04:00</updated><title type='text'>Fabric stores, Project Runway.</title><content type='html'>&lt;i&gt;A forewarning:  Based upon this post's title, you are probably thinking this will be yet another classic Lauren anecdote.  Well actually, this is a Josh post.  And yes, it takes place at a fabric store.  Finally, there is a discussion of Project Runway -- season spoiler ALERT.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Yesterday, Lauren became inspired with some ideas for decorating the apartment for the changing season and wanted to make a run to Jo-Ann fabric store.  I obliged after being fed well at Quizno's.  So off we went...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I dropped her off at the door so she could get a head start, but immediately upon doing so, I realized that I'd be the lone male soldier walking into the store all by myself -- uncharted territory.  I had a slight panic attack, but it graciously receded quickly.  I think the panic was due to the fact that I thought I was doing a very efficient (albeit typical male) shopping exercise, only to have the reality of entering the store alone thrown back in my face.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Slight side note:  Next to Jo-Ann (can't stand that hyphen in their name, btw), is a golf store on one side (all husbands, males rejoice!) and another feminine-type craft store.  2 to 1, ladies win.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As I walked in the store I tried to convince myself that I was both Michael Knight and Jeffery Sebelia from Project Runway; manly and confident, yet in touch with his creative, problem solving side.  I couldn't BELIEVE the lines in the place.  They wound throughout the store -- multiple lines, in fact.  A line to get your fabric cut to size, and another winding line to check out.  We later found out it was part of the Halloween preparations.  I find Lauren and she has a handfull of items already handy, but the main thing she was after was red fabric that matched other items in our decor.  She was about to call it quits before I said we needed to check out a promising looking corner of the store.  There it was.  The winning piece.  With boosted confidence, I found myself shooting across to other aisles to find complimenting fabrics.  I went over the edge.  Tiffany, you would have been so, so proud.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Project Runway.  Aren't we all a little depressed that Jeffery won?  Sure, he was the most consistent and innovative throughout the season, but one area in which he wasn't innovative was his little attitude problem.  As Lauren might say to that statement, "Hmph!"  It really annoyed me that here he is, doing some really interesting work, but had nothing but the typical artist chip on his shoulder and attitude to give back to other people.  Even upon winning, &lt;a href="http://www.realityblurred.com/realitytv/index.php?page=2"&gt;his demeanor persisted.&lt;/a&gt;  Just had to get that rant out there . . . any other observations on the season?  We wanted Uli to win, darnit!</content><link rel='alternate' type='text/html' href='http://www.thefairskinneditalians.com/2006/10/fabric-stores-project-runway.html' title='Fabric stores, Project Runway.'/><link rel='replies' type='text/html' href='http://www.blogger.com/comment.g?blogID=11910755&amp;postID=116156707393819935' title='4 Comments'/><link rel='replies' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://www.thefairskinneditalians.com/feeds/main-atom.xml' title='Post Comments'/><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://www.blogger.com/feeds/11910755/posts/default/116156707393819935'/><link rel='edit' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://www.blogger.com/feeds/11910755/posts/default/116156707393819935'/><author><name>Josh</name></author></entry><entry><id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-11910755.post-116114237185684175</id><published>2006-10-17T23:29:00.000-04:00</published><updated>2006-10-17T23:36:00.193-04:00</updated><title type='text'>New website feature.</title><content type='html'>Hello faithful readers:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Just wanted to let you in on the latest addition in the sidebar over to the right.  We've added a "Recent Comments" area so you can follow comment dialogue in a much easier fashion.  Of course, if you want to continue to check comment updates in your own way, that is still possible.  Thanks again for reading, even though our posts have become a bit more erratic.  We're working to improve that. =)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This post is also an attempt to get that beautiful toilet photograph further down and ultimately off the front page.</content><link rel='alternate' type='text/html' href='http://www.thefairskinneditalians.com/2006/10/new-website-feature.html' title='New website feature.'/><link rel='replies' type='text/html' href='http://www.blogger.com/comment.g?blogID=11910755&amp;postID=116114237185684175' title='0 Comments'/><link rel='replies' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://www.thefairskinneditalians.com/feeds/main-atom.xml' title='Post Comments'/><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://www.blogger.com/feeds/11910755/posts/default/116114237185684175'/><link rel='edit' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://www.blogger.com/feeds/11910755/posts/default/116114237185684175'/><author><name>Josh</name></author></entry><entry><id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-11910755.post-116024835429954332</id><published>2006-10-07T15:01:00.000-04:00</published><updated>2006-10-07T15:12:34.353-04:00</updated><title type='text'>Farewell, Final Candidate.</title><content type='html'>Well we hope your Saturday was better than Lauren and mine's.  We attended a funeral of Nemo sized proportions.  My Beta fish "Final Candidate" died today after an attempt to clean his water vase home.  I cleaned his murky water bowl, attempted to feed him and noticed he was acting very strange since I placed him back in his home.  He was swimming upside-down, sideways, and anyway but the right way.  We're afraid it might have been brain damage due to lack of oxgen in the transfer from dirty bowl to clean bowl.  So sad.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;He'd get to the water's surface, only to be dragged back down to the little pebbles below moments later.  We left him to get lunch and told him he could die in peace without anyone to watch him . . . he did just that.  Gone is my lively desktop friend.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is a photo from the funeral we held for Final Candidate.  He lived a good, faithful life.  Farewell, friend.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.thefairskinneditalians.com/img/IMG_6916.jpg"&gt;</content><link rel='alternate' type='text/html' href='http://www.thefairskinneditalians.com/2006/10/farewell-final-candidate.html' title='Farewell, Final Candidate.'/><link rel='replies' type='text/html' href='http://www.blogger.com/comment.g?blogID=11910755&amp;postID=116024835429954332' title='6 Comments'/><link rel='replies' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://www.thefairskinneditalians.com/feeds/main-atom.xml' title='Post Comments'/><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://www.blogger.com/feeds/11910755/posts/default/116024835429954332'/><link rel='edit' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://www.blogger.com/feeds/11910755/posts/default/116024835429954332'/><author><name>Josh</name></author></entry><entry><id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-11910755.post-115923742964746568</id><published>2006-09-25T21:24:00.000-04:00</published><updated>2006-09-25T22:40:14.966-04:00</updated><title type='text'>Classroom Stories Anthology Part 1</title><content type='html'>Here's possibly the first of a random compilation of some of the most humorous (and/or pitifully heartbreaking) moments yet to be experienced this year. &lt;br /&gt;Here we go.....&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A couple of weeks ago we were practicing our Test Behavior. The IOWA test was coming up (remember that?!?) and I was determined to get those kids trained to NOT TALK during the test. So during one of our last practices before the real thing, I was helping a student when I heard a quiet "Uh, Mrs. Teague?" to which I whirled around and gave this student The Look. Which was followed by, "Honey, if that happens again, you know you'll have to pull a card, right?" "Yes, Ma'am." "Okay, then. Raise your hand and I'll call on you in a minute." Two minutes later, I turned around to address the said student's question and realized she was holding a handful of her own noseblood.&lt;br /&gt;How none of it got on her spiritwear t-shirt is beyond my comprehension.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We were working on thank you notes to our local police station for Public Safety Week. Then this conversation happened.&lt;br /&gt;Student: "Mrs. Teague, my dad's been in jail before."&lt;br /&gt;Me (smoothly nonchalant) : "oh?"&lt;br /&gt;Student: "Yeah, my mom called the police. They had a fight....they're not married anymore."*&lt;br /&gt;(This story doesn't sound funny at all, but you have to understand that the child said it completely matter of factly and as if this happens all the time. I was also acting like this happens all the time. The other kids who overheard had their jaws on the ground, but myself and this kid, we were cool, man.)  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A student walked over to my table to show me a Presidential Biography book.&lt;br /&gt;"Mrs. Teague, I know who this book is about."&lt;br /&gt;"Who?"&lt;br /&gt;"George Washington."&lt;br /&gt;"You're right."&lt;br /&gt;"I miss him...he was a good President."&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I was grading a piece of writing which included a family trip to Goody's, where her father "bought a white beeder."&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The new girl came to school with a note from her mom, who was concerned that another student was "making fun of her." &lt;br /&gt;I brought that student up to the Teacher's Desk, and she very calmly explained to me that she hadn't meant to hurt anyone's feelings. I told her to turn to the new student and say exactly to her what she told me. The student immediately broke down crying. Guilt? Shame? I'll never really know. &lt;br /&gt;This is about the third time I've made a student cry this year. Another incident included a student who swears he was NOT the one throwing his sandwhich on the ground in the cafeteria. (Despite eyewitness accounts.)&lt;br /&gt;The third time was when a student scribbled all over her paper with a highlighter and I asked her not to do that again. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There's one student in my class who will raise his hand everyday and wait for five minutes during breakfast time until I call on him. And everyday all he wants to tell me is, "I don't want my milk." Every. Day. I tell him to go ahead and throw it away and he doesn't have to check. Doesn't matter. It happens everyday.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I also want to take this opportunity to mention that I have one of the lowest of the Low Talkers ever known to mankind in my class this year. Not only that, she also wants to answer every question. Most class discussions end up like this.&lt;br /&gt;Me "What do you think?" (or some other teacher question)&lt;br /&gt;Low Talker raises her hand. I make a mental sigh, prepare and call on her.&lt;br /&gt;Low Talker whispers inaudibly.&lt;br /&gt;Me: "What?"&lt;br /&gt;Whisper repeats but does not increase in volume.&lt;br /&gt;Me: "I'm sorry hon, I canNOT hear you."&lt;br /&gt;More whispers, still much too quiet to understand.&lt;br /&gt;Me:"Uh, okay, say it one more time for me?"&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At this point, one of two things happen. The kids around her interrupt our little game out of exasperation and tell me what she said OR, I yell at her "SAY IT REALLY LOUD....REALLY LOUD....LOUDER THAN THAT...oh, yes you can use the restroom."&lt;br /&gt;It's gotten so bad I'm making a point to bring it up at conferences tomorrow.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I will say this the second year has been MUCH, MUCH, calmer and generally more productive than last. Praise God!! I DO like this job!</content><link rel='alternate' type='text/html' href='http://www.thefairskinneditalians.com/2006/09/classroom-stories-anthology-part-1.html' title='Classroom Stories Anthology Part 1'/><link rel='replies' type='text/html' href='http://www.blogger.com/comment.g?blogID=11910755&amp;postID=115923742964746568' title='6 Comments'/><link rel='replies' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://www.thefairskinneditalians.com/feeds/main-atom.xml' title='Post Comments'/><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://www.blogger.com/feeds/11910755/posts/default/115923742964746568'/><link rel='edit' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://www.blogger.com/feeds/11910755/posts/default/115923742964746568'/><author><name>Lauren</name></author></entry><entry><id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-11910755.post-115569845712422757</id><published>2006-08-15T23:20:00.000-04:00</published><updated>2006-08-16T22:07:05.546-04:00</updated><title type='text'>Top Ten Signs your Second Grade Class is Too Attached to Their Class Pet</title><content type='html'>(a Betta fish, in this case)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;10. While practicing democracy, when the class was allowed to vote on names (suggested by classmates), the runners up are Rosy, Blue, and Kim. (It's a blue fish. Not sure how Rosy was such a popular vote.) The winning name- King.*&lt;br /&gt;9. The kids ask daily, "Is it a girl fish or a boy fish?" and are not satisfied with "whichever you want." Even after being declared a boy fish, the students still take a daily, independent vote when they think teacher is not watching.&lt;br /&gt;8.  If teacher forgets to say, "Good Morning, King" after announcements, she is quickly reminded by at least two volunteers.&lt;br /&gt;6. While building Classroom Community and practicing the delicate arts of complimenting, one child requests to give King a compliment. Said request granted,  and ten more hands shoot up into the air. (The class appears to think King's strengths include being a good swimmer and a good friend)&lt;br /&gt;5. While playing Name Bingo during same said Community Time, students request to know why King's name is missing from the Bingo cards containing the class roster.&lt;br /&gt;4. At the end of the day, students are encouraged to remember the day's activities and finish the sentence, "I had a great day because....." Everyday, one student will wave hand enthusiastically and when called on, (by a teacher thinking, "Oh! They really had a great day for some reason! I must be a great teacher!")  will ask to go see King for a minute. Another hand up. Eventual mass exodus by class to fish bowl as they wait for their bus to be called.&lt;br /&gt;3. The aforesaid Exodus to the fish bowl is the only time the shyest student in class will actually raise his hand to ask a question. Imagine a child who says very little all day whispering, "May I go see the fish?" with bright and hopeful eyes.&lt;br /&gt;2. During silent reading time, students request to read to King. By some strange miracle from heaven, the fish actually swims to the edge of the bowl to look at the pictures as the kids turn the pages.&lt;br /&gt;1. And finally, the #1 Reason you know your classroom is too attached to their pet:&lt;br /&gt; On the way to the bus ramp last Friday, the students were very concerned that their teacher was leaving King alone for the WHOLE WEEKEND with NO FOOD. Stories of pet fish deaths ineveitably to follow throughout the remainder of the five minute bus ramp walk. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;*The rejected fish name suggestions that nobody voted for except the one kid who thought of it: Becca, Rebecca (two friends suggesting names one after another here), Nemo and Roofoos.</content><link rel='alternate' type='text/html' href='http://www.thefairskinneditalians.com/2006/08/top-ten-signs-your-second-grade-class_15.html' title='Top Ten Signs your Second Grade Class is Too Attached to Their Class Pet'/><link rel='replies' type='text/html' href='http://www.blogger.com/comment.g?blogID=11910755&amp;postID=115569845712422757' title='7 Comments'/><link rel='replies' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://www.thefairskinneditalians.com/feeds/main-atom.xml' title='Post Comments'/><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://www.blogger.com/feeds/11910755/posts/default/115569845712422757'/><link rel='edit' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://www.blogger.com/feeds/11910755/posts/default/115569845712422757'/><author><name>Lauren</name></author></entry><entry><id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-11910755.post-115440793366512759</id><published>2006-08-01T00:51:00.000-04:00</published><updated>2006-08-01T00:55:05.703-04:00</updated><title type='text'>Happy Birthday, Josh!!!</title><content type='html'>&lt;img src="http://www.thefairskinneditalians.com/img/group-surprise.jpg"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Despite the odds, Josh seemed to be successfully surprised at his party. There were a couple of challenges to pull this thing off. For starters, Josh is working from home, as am I (sort of) since it's summer. And he doesn't leave the apartment. Ever. And the apartment has partitions instead of walls, so a phone conversation can be heard throughout every square foot.&lt;br /&gt;But I was determined and a few factors actually worked in my favor. Like Josh didn't find it too weird that I randomly started taking my cell phone with me on walks. And  he has no sense of errand timing and thought nothing of it when I was gone for three hours to supposedly go grocery shopping. (And didn't check my trunk to find Party City bags) I think it also helps that all of his friends are so honest that Josh completely trusts them and anything they say. ("Uh...I think we're already doing something Friday, but I'm not sure....")&lt;br /&gt;So with some major help from Andy, Jill, Mike, and Will, I took Josh out to eat while they came in, decorated, set up food, and had the whole apartment rearranged to suit a party-sized crowd. He was incredibly shocked when he walked in and about 20 people were piled on top of the couch in the corner of the room yelling SURPRISE!!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Of course, we had some close calls. Here's just a few:&lt;br /&gt;1) I printed a picture of Josh's face to cut out as part of the centerpiece. When he came back from volunteering at church, the first thing I heard him say- "Why is there a picture of me on the computer?" My feeble attempt at an answer,"Oh, I missed you while you were gone all morning and went through old pictures." (Yup, he bought it.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2) Someone sent me an instant gmail message that popped up on my screen and read, "Thanks for the directions, but you forgot to give the apartment number." Thankfully, I saw it and took it down before Josh noticed.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;3) Gmail pops up a window to let you know whenever you have a new email, including the name of sender and the first line from the email -- for example, "'We'd love to come to the party!" I could NOT figure out how to turn this feature off, and Josh uses my computer a lot for work. So I kinda made up that he had to turn it off or he might see a confirmation email about a gift I (didn't really) ordered online for him. Bought that one, too.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And finally,&lt;br /&gt;4)After we ate dinner the night of, Josh starts pushing to go get ice cream. Naturally, he thought it was weird of me to refuse to go. I pulled the whole "I'm just SO TIRED" routine. (Translation- "There's 20 people waiting for you at the apartment!!") But he just needed that ice cream and made the decision to stop at Kroger. Where he did not let me run in to get it alone (heart skipping a beat), he took his time walking in ( cold sweat) and did not want to leave the magazine section. (minor nausia.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;But we made it home, finally. It was really touching to see how many people made that extra effort to come from out of town or in the middle of busy summer schedules.&lt;br /&gt;I don't think this surprise would have been possible if Josh wasn't as loving and trusting as he is. When I asked him to fix my gmail so he wouldn't see the emails coming into it, he did it. When I begged him to take me home instead of getting the ice cream he was so obviously craving, he actually apologized that he forgot that I must be feeling so tired. And Josh allows me a lot of freedom, so he doesn't question where I go shopping or constantly check the online banking to see how much I spent. (Note to self: I must never use these powers for evil.) &lt;br /&gt;Josh, I think the only reason you had a great surprise is because you put so much trust and faith in your family and friends. &lt;br /&gt;Thanks, Birthday Man. Happy 25th!!!</content><link rel='alternate' type='text/html' href='http://www.thefairskinneditalians.com/2006/08/happy-birthday-josh_01.html' title='Happy Birthday, Josh!!!'/><link rel='replies' type='text/html' href='http://www.blogger.com/comment.g?blogID=11910755&amp;postID=115440793366512759' title='3 Comments'/><link rel='replies' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://www.thefairskinneditalians.com/feeds/main-atom.xml' title='Post Comments'/><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://www.blogger.com/feeds/11910755/posts/default/115440793366512759'/><link rel='edit' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://www.blogger.com/feeds/11910755/posts/default/115440793366512759'/><author><name>Lauren</name></author></entry><entry><id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-11910755.post-115377721253818543</id><published>2006-07-24T17:19:00.000-04:00</published><updated>2006-07-24T17:40:12.933-04:00</updated><title type='text'>The Gate Story</title><content type='html'>Last week, Josh's mom was scheduled to come over and pick me up. (TWO broken Teague sewing machines- we HAD to get them to Joe the repairman as quickly as possible). After a very cheerful knock on the door, Mrs. Teague walked in, gave us some cookies, and was generally quite sunny and content.&lt;br /&gt;It wasn't until about a full minute of greetings and conversation later that she mentioned that she needed our help. As she was driving through the gate, it slammed shut and left a scratch on her Porshe.&lt;br /&gt;Josh immediately left with her to go talk to the manager of the apartment. The manager's first response was somewhat of denial. He told Mrs. Teague that it wasn't that he didn't believe her, but, well, "no one saw it happen." Josh-he's quick and asked him if the camera aimed at the gate hadn't caught any of the action on tape. No, no, that camera just for monitoring, not taping. (No one was monitoring at the time.) The manager then got the idea to have Maxine, the leasing agent, drive her car through the gate.&lt;br /&gt;If Mrs. Teague's car needed a band-aid, Maxine's car needed needed a stiff sling and a leg cast. The gate completely dinged in the side of her car while leaving a nice, long scratch.&lt;br /&gt;The really sympathetic part of the story is after Maxine told the managerthat gate had, in her words, "killed her car," the manager replied (to Josh and his mother), "Well, that's good for you." &lt;br /&gt;He then went about contacting the gate company.&lt;br /&gt;The coolest part is that after Mrs. Teague and I left, Josh had an idea for a good deed.&lt;br /&gt;Remember that Mrs. Teague brought us cookies? She baked them for Josh because she felt like God wanted her to. Being the trusting Christian she is, she followed even though she wasn't sure why cookies would suddenly be important.&lt;br /&gt;Well, Josh decided to give them to the manager and Maxine to ease the feelings of everyone involved in a- wait, two- gate accidentS.&lt;br /&gt;Of course, they were impressed, grateful, and caught by surprise.&lt;br /&gt;That's Josh, his mother, and God working together for you.</content><link rel='alternate' type='text/html' href='http://www.thefairskinneditalians.com/2006/07/gate-story.html' title='The Gate Story'/><link rel='replies' type='text/html' href='http://www.blogger.com/comment.g?blogID=11910755&amp;postID=115377721253818543' title='1 Comments'/><link rel='replies' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://www.thefairskinneditalians.com/feeds/main-atom.xml' title='Post Comments'/><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://www.blogger.com/feeds/11910755/posts/default/115377721253818543'/><link rel='edit' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://www.blogger.com/feeds/11910755/posts/default/115377721253818543'/><author><name>Lauren</name></author></entry><entry><id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-11910755.post-115354166810402587</id><published>2006-07-22T00:08:00.000-04:00</published><updated>2006-07-22T00:24:05.913-04:00</updated><title type='text'>New RSS Feed address.</title><content type='html'>Quick technical update.  For those who subscribe to this site through an RSS reader, please update the location of the feed to: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;block&gt;&lt;a href="http://feeds.feedburner.com/thefairskinneditalians"&gt;http://feeds.feedburner.com/thefairskinneditalians&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/block&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you're not sure what all that means, don't worry about it...  But if you read a lot of blogs and sites, &lt;a href="http://www.mrexcel.com/tip108.shtml"&gt;RSS might be helpful&lt;/a&gt; to you in keeping up with sites without having to reload them every day to see if there's updates.</content><link rel='alternate' type='text/html' href='http://www.thefairskinneditalians.com/2006/07/new-rss-feed-address.html' title='New RSS Feed address.'/><link rel='replies' type='text/html' href='http://www.blogger.com/comment.g?blogID=11910755&amp;postID=115354166810402587' title='0 Comments'/><link rel='replies' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://www.thefairskinneditalians.com/feeds/main-atom.xml' title='Post Comments'/><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://www.blogger.com/feeds/11910755/posts/default/115354166810402587'/><link rel='edit' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://www.blogger.com/feeds/11910755/posts/default/115354166810402587'/><author><name>Josh</name></author></entry><entry><id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-11910755.post-115309762213545015</id><published>2006-07-16T20:33:00.000-04:00</published><updated>2006-07-18T09:56:44.583-04:00</updated><title type='text'>Celebrating the First Year</title><content type='html'>When we started this blog over a year (!) ago, we used the first post to thank people for everything they had been doing for us and our engagement. Tonight as we ate a delicious dinner prepared by Josh, we talked about all the amazing things we've done and people we've met during our first year of marriage.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This year was a busy, crazy year! We joined up with our awesome community group, I started my first job, and I only threatened to quit my first job twice. Josh threatened to quit his first job and actually followed through. Thus sending him off to grad school while I move into a second year of teaching that is supposed to be easier than the first. (Prayers accepted.) Josh got his wedding ring resized- twice.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Josh won his first design award, complete with a trip to Paris, we went to four weddings of friends of ours, welcomed a new niece, and the first of our friends had a baby boy. We celebrated Silas's first birthday, moved Annie into her freshman dorm, had two sets of friends get engaged, and went on our first helicopter ride. And saw Mount Rushmore and the Eiffel Tower. Not to mention the Anna Ruby Falls we visited just yesterday. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We thank Jesus for his blessings and faithfulness in our marriage this year.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We could go on, but pictures are worth so many  more words. So here's about 50,000 words summed up into little moments captured on film. Err -- on digital screens from the past year. Some you'll remember, some are new. Enjoy them all!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;object classid="clsid:d27cdb6e-ae6d-11cf-96b8-444553540000" codebase="http://fpdownload.macromedia.com/pub/shockwave/cabs/flash/swflash.cab#version=7,0,0,0" width="504" height="400" id="slideshow" align="middle"&gt;&lt;param name="allowScriptAccess" value="sameDomain" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;param name="movie" value="http://www.thefairskinneditalians.com/slideshow-2.swf" /&gt;&lt;param name="quality" value="high" /&gt;&lt;param name="bgcolor" value="#ffffff" /&gt;&lt;embed src="http://www.thefairskinneditalians.com/slideshow-2.swf" quality="high" bgcolor="#ffffff" width="504" height="400" name="slideshow" align="middle" allowScriptAccess="sameDomain" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" pluginspage="http://www.macromedia.com/go/getflashplayer" /&gt;&lt;/embed&gt;&lt;/object&gt;</content><link rel='alternate' type='text/html' href='http://www.thefairskinneditalians.com/2006/07/celebrating-first-year.html' title='Celebrating the First Year'/><link rel='replies' type='text/html' href='http://www.blogger.com/comment.g?blogID=11910755&amp;postID=115309762213545015' title='7 Comments'/><link rel='replies' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://www.thefairskinneditalians.com/feeds/main-atom.xml' title='Post Comments'/><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://www.blogger.com/feeds/11910755/posts/default/115309762213545015'/><link rel='edit' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://www.blogger.com/feeds/11910755/posts/default/115309762213545015'/><author><name>Lauren</name></author></entry></feed>